

Muhammad Amir

Fahmy

- **\(\begin{align*}
 \hline +6013-7746263 \end{align*}
 \end{align*}**
- amir12102009@gmail.com
- Taman Cheng Baru, Melaka, Malaysia
- khunamir.github.io/portfolio-2.0



PROFILE



My name is Muhammad Amir Fahmy. I am currently a 25 years old Software and Automation Developer with 1 year plus of experience. I also hold a Bachelor of Information Systems (Hons.) Intelligent Systems Engineering. I have a deep interest in Data Science and Text Analytics (Natural Language Processing). I am a certified Data Science Professional by IBM and also a certified Power BI Data Analyst Associate by Microsoft. I love to read, finish courses, and find new things to learn. I am looking to apply all my industrial and academic knowledge in a related position and continue to expand my knowledge in an industrial environment.

EXPERIENCE



Oct 2023 - Current

Software & Automation Developer

Aspiro Sdn Bhd

Shah Alam, Selangor

- In charge of daily operational support for multiple automation projects running in production
 - Code debugging (C# and Automation Anywhere) and database monitoring through MSSQL queries
- Going through the whole Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) to develop new automation project
- Cooperate with Business Analysts to communicate with clients in understanding requirements and SAP Business Processes
- Championed the team's Microsoft Teams notification project to notify PICs of automation errors straight through the teams channel utilizing the Graph API

Mar 2023 - Aug 2023

Software & Automation Apprentice

KPMG Malaysia (Lighthouse)

Petaling Jaya, Selangor

- Develop new website for internal client using Django regarding Malaysian Business Reporting System (MBRS)
- Experienced meeting with clients
- Conduct UAT testing
- In charge of reviewers module

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020

IT Intern

Batu Berendam, Melaka

- Assist in proposal creation for new website projects
- Update products information in client's e-commerce website
- Experience web consultation communication with clients
- Assists in setting up Personal Computers for a new client's office

EDUCATION



Merpati Blue

May 2021 - Aug 2023

Bachelor of Information System (Hons.)

Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM)

Intelligent Sytems Engineering

Shah Alam, Selangor

- Published a paper on IEEE through the 2022 3rd International Conference on Artificial Intelligence and Data Science (AiDAS)
- Participated in a programming competition (Mini Pro-solve)
- Graduated with Vice Chancellor's Award (CGPA 3.72)
- Quarter-finalist for Inter-faculty Sports, Quarter-finalist for Lions League, Champion for Inter-program Sports (Badminton)

Sep 2018 - Mar 2021

Diploma in Computer Science

Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM)

Jasin, Melaka

- Graduated with Vice Chancellor's Award (CGPA 3.81)
- President of UiTM Jasin Cycling Club

PROJECTS

o

- Sports Diet Fuzzy Based Expert System (React Native, Django)
- Badminton Hobbyist Fee Payment Web Application (React)
- Topic Modeling of Science and Technology News (Natural Language Processing)

CERTIFICATIONS



- IBM Data Science Professional
- Microsoft Certified: Power BI Data Analyst Associate
- Certified Data Analyst Associate (Asia Pacific University of Technology and Innovation)
- Certified Entry-level Python Programmer (Python Institute)